Guide to the Jerome New Frank Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- BOOKS OF JEROME FRANK, Series IX
  - Given to MS & Arch 12/11/73
    - Basic Works of Aristotle --- edited by Richard McKeon (Box 216)
    - The New American Right--- edited by Daniel Bell (Box 216)
    - The Lonely Crowd--- David Riesman (Box 218)
    - The Course of American Democratic Thought--- Ralph Henry Gabriel (Box 218)
    - The Idea of History --- R.G. Collingwood (Box 218)
    - The Lost World of Thomas Jefferson--- Daniel J. Boorstin (Box 214)
    - The American Scholar (Vol 20) (Box 218)
    - The American Scholar (Vol.19) (Box 218)
    - The American Scholar (Vol.21) (Box 218)
    - The American Scholar (Vol.17) (Box 218)
    - The American Scholar (Vol.18) (Box 218)
    - Personality & Political Crisis --- Edited by Alfred H. Stanton & Stewart E. Perry (Box 218)
    - Revival of Realism --- James Feibleman (Box 216)
    - he England of Elizabeth --- A.L. Rowse (Box 218)
    - People in Quandaries --- Wendell Johnson (Box 218)
  - Given 12/14/1973
    - Recollections (Vol I) --- Viscount John Morley (Box 214)
    - Recollections (Vol II) (Box 216)
    - Criminal Law in Action --- John B. Waite (Box 216)
    - Language, Thought, & Reality--- edited by John B. Carroll (Box 216)
    - American Journal of Psychiatry--- July 1940 (Box 216)
    - An Index to Aristotle --- Troy W. Organ (Box 216)
    - The Modern Theme --- Jose Ortega y Gasset (Box 215)
    - The Eagle Screams --- Coley Taylor & Samuel Middlebrook (Box 216)
    - Living Law of Democratic Society--- Jerome Hall (Box 215)
    - Principles of Sociology (vol II) --- Herbert Spencer (Box 215)
    - Methods of the Sciences (Pt. II) (Box 216)
    - God and Country --- Charles Schoenfeld (Box 216)
    - World's Greatest Literature (Hegel) (Box 216)
    - Democracy in America (2 vols) --- Alexis de Tocqueville (Box 216)
    - Introduction to Reflective Thinking--- Columbia Associates in Philosophy (Box 216)
    - Politicians and Moralists of the 19th Cent. --- Emile Faguet (Box 216)
    - The Sinews of Peace --- Herbert Feis (Box 216)
    - Outline of Psychanalysis --- edited by Clara Thompson (Box 215)
    - Basic Teachings of the Great Economists-- John W. McConnell (Box 216)
    - Works of Charles Lamb(vol II) (Box 215)
    - Politics of Philo Judaeus --- Edwin R. Goodenough (Box 215)
    - The Subtle Knot --- Margaret L. Wiley (Box 215)
    - Psychological Types--- C. G. Jung (Box 215)
    - Macaulay's Essays (Vol I) (Box 215)
    - Justice Oliver Wendel Holmes--- Silas Bent (Box 214)
    - Village-Communities in the East & West --- Sir Henry S. Maine (Box 214)
    - Decadence --- Remy de Gourmount (Box 214)
    - Ancient Art and Ritual --- Jane E. Hamson (Box 214)
    - Gibbon On Christianity (Box 214)
    - Patterns of Educational Philosophy --- Theodore Brameld (Box 214)
    - Bench and Bar --- William Durran (Box 215)
    - The Historian and Historical Evidence --- Allen Johnson (Box 214)
    - Architects of Ideas--- Ernest R. Trattner (Box 215)
    - History of the Organization of the Sciences (Box 214)
    - Freud's Contribution to Psychiatry --- A.A. Brill (Box 214)
    - Capitalism, Socialism and Democracy --- Joseph A. Schumpeter (Box 214)
    - A Student's History of Philosophy --- Arthur K Rogers (Box 215)
    - The Making of Man --- edited by V.F. Calverton (Box 214)
    - Pascal's Pensees (Box 214)
    - The Legacy of Greece --- Edited by R. W. Livingstone (Box 214)
    - The Hedgehog and the Fox --- Isaiah Berlin (Box 214)
    - Cicero's Tusculan Disputation (Box 214)
    - The Dialogues of Plato --- B. Jowett (Box 215)
- RESEARCH MATERIAL
  This unarranged material, which includes notes and printed matter, is contained in nineteen cartons. The cartons are numbered from 190 to 208 inclusive.
  - Research notes and printed matter (Box 190)
  - Research notes and printed matter (Box 191)
  - Research notes and printed matter (Box 192)
  - Research notes and printed matter (Box 193)
  - Research notes and printed matter (Box 194)
  - Research notes and printed matter (Box 195)
  - Research notes and printed matter (Box 196)
  - Research notes and printed matter (Box 197)
  - Research notes and printed matter (Box 198)
  - Research notes and printed matter (Box 199)
  - Research notes and printed matter (Box 200)
  - Research notes and printed matter (Box 201)
  - Research notes and printed matter (Box 202)
  - Research notes and printed matter (Box 203)
  - Research notes and printed matter (Box 204)
  - Research notes and printed matter (Box 205)
  - Research notes and printed matter (Box 206)
  - Research notes and printed matter (Box 207)
  - Research notes and printed matter (Box 208)
- Restricted, 1945-1957 (Box 212)
  This box contains the following files, which are restricted until 2032: Box 118, selected material from folders 1142-1146, series V; Box 178, folders 1 and 2, series VII; Box 179, folders 12, 16, 17, series VII; one folder of restricted correspondence containing items pulled from series IV (alphabetically arranged correspondence) and two items of Charles Kiper from series VIII.
  Conditions Governing Access
  Materials are restricted until January 1, 2032 due to privacy concerns.
- Additional Material, ACCESSION 1986-M-108
  - The Bramble Bush: annotated volume and notes, 1930 (Box 209)